<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[FlowER]]></title>
  <link href="copyme.github.io/flower/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="copyme.github.io/flower/"/>
  <updated>2014-05-13T22:18:15+02:00</updated>
  <id>copyme.github.io/flower/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Copyme & Meri-nut]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dragon, Bunny and New Flows]]></title>
    <link href="copyme.github.io/flower/blog/2014/04/25/dragon/"/>
    <updated>2014-04-25T21:52:32+02:00</updated>
    <id>copyme.github.io/flower/blog/2014/04/25/dragon</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Last few days we sent on implementation of two new flows. Both are an extension of well known mean curvature flows. In the first case we have added a boundary case for meshes which are not close.
Second case is a variation of mean curvature flow which is obtained by intensification of components of curvature vector by given power. As you can see e.g. for cylinder we obtained rounded result
than for standard mean curvature flow. </p>

<p>Second news is related to movies which present mean curvature flow of more complex meshes. So in media category you can find movies which presents flow of well known Stanford dragon and bunny.</p>

<p>At the end we would like to inform you that we have gotten a feedback from one person about our project and this person pointed out that we should create a section on web page about theoretical
aspects of flows. We think this is a good idea and we will work on this in the next few day. Stay tuned!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let's Get Ready to Rumble!]]></title>
    <link href="copyme.github.io/flower/blog/2014/04/12/Lets-get-ready-to-rumble/"/>
    <updated>2014-04-12T02:41:13+02:00</updated>
    <id>copyme.github.io/flower/blog/2014/04/12/Lets-get-ready-to-rumble</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Last few weeks we have been spending on study of curvature flows and fruit of this work is a piece of software - FlowER. At the beginning we wanted to generate only some output files
and forget about whole code. But during one rainy weekend one of us added support for OpenGL and cleaned up some strange parts of the code. 
After that we started to think about releasing of our work. And finally we give you access to it under agreements of great license - GPL 2. On this page we will share some news and e.g. movies
which presents given flows in action. Maybe we will add some theoretical parts too. </p>

<p>We done some efforts to make FlowER easy to use for students which are interested in implementations of flows. Also if you are a teacher probably you will be interested to use FlowER during your
courses to show how flows work and also FlowER allows you to give students some homeworks, and they can directly focus on flows and forget about all other stuff like data presentation.</p>

<p>We have a hope that FlowER will be useful and thus we are waiting for any feedback from you! Also if you have some movies which present flows implemented by you please share them with us and
we will put them on this web page. To share anything please use our issue tracker.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
